Report
to your stations immediately.
This is not a drill.
We are under attack!
- Shit!
- Language!
Jarvis, what's the view from upstairs?
The central building is
protected by some kind
of energy shield.
Strucker's technology is well beyond
any other Hydra base we've taken.
Loki's sceptre must be here.
Strucker couldn't
mount this defence without it.
At long last.
"At long last" is lasting
a little long, boys.
Yeah. I think we lost
the element of surprise.
Wait a second.
No one else is gonna deal with the fact
that Cap just said "Language"?
I know.
Just slipped out.
Who gave the order to attack?
Herr Strucker, it's the Avengers.
They landed in the far woods.
The perimeter guard panicked.
They have to be after the sceptre.
- Can we hold them?
- They're the Avengers.
Deploy the rest of the tanks.
Concentrate fire on the weak ones.
A hit may make them close ranks.
Everything we've accomplished...
But we're on the verge
of our greatest breakthrough.
Then let's show them
what we've accomplished.
Send out the twins.
It's too soon.
It's what they signed up for.
My men can hold them.
Sir, the city is taking fire.
Well, we know Strucker's not gonna
worry about civilian casualties.
Send in the Iron Legion.
This quadrant is unsafe.
Please back away.